//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answer
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "The Great 'what' of London occurred in 1666?",
        answer: "Fire",
        options: [
            "Fire",
            "Flood"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What was Queen Mary of England's nickname?",
        answer: "Bloody",
        options: [
            "Virgin",
            "Bloody"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Elizabeth I of England was known as the 'what' Queen?",
        answer: "Virgin",
        options: [
            "Virgin",
            "Bloody"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What was the relationship between Mary and Elizabeth of England?",
        answer: "Half-Sisters",
        options: [
            "Half-Sisters",
            "Cousins"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What was Marie Curie most famous for being?",
        answer: "Scientist",
        options: [
            "Scientist",
            "Actress"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The Aztecs were conquered by which European country?",
        answer: "Spain",
        options: [
            "Portugal",
            "Spain"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The Aztecs lived primarily in the region known as what today?",
        answer: "Mexico",
        options: [
            "Cuba",
            "Mexico"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What was New York's original name?",
        answer: "New Amsterdam",
        options: [
            "New Amsterdam",
            "The Big Apple"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which energy source was important for the advances of the Industrial Revolution?",
        answer: "Coal",
        options: [
            "Coal",
            "Gas"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The Shoguns ruled over which country?",
        answer: "Japan",
        options: [
            "China",
            "Japan"
        ]
    },

];